[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
PARK MINJAE'S LIST
START DATING...
BETWEEN STEPS
IN MEMORY OF DIRECTOR AHN PANSUK
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS, AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
THIS DRAMA CONTAINS SENSITIVE CONTENT
[staff] Mr. Park Minjae, we're done. Thank you for your patience.
Take your time getting up.
Take it slow, and hold onto this here.
Let's try walking a few steps.
[Minjae] Yes.
[staff] You said it was a little tight, so I made some adjustments.
Go ahead and take a few steps.
Slowly. Yeah.
[staff] How is it? Is it okay?
Yeah. I think it's okay.
[doctor] It's clean.
Uh, does that mean I'm still in remission?
[doctor] Yes, that's right.
There's no sign of it spreading anywhere else, and everything looks good.
Well, you're young, so...
After five years of complete remission, you're generally considered cured.
You're 10 years in remission.
Keep up your regular check-ups, and you'll be fine.
But it's still cancer.
Can I really just let my guard down like that?
[doctor] Yes, eat well and exercise.
Just keep taking good care of yourself.
You can live just like anyone else.
Okay, I will.
EPISODE 1
DON'T BRUSH YOUR TEETH IN THE KITCHEN
Answer the phone. I'm brushing my teeth.
Hello.
-Hel... -[line beeping]
Damn it.
You could've picked that up.
-They'll call back if it's urgent. -[keyboard clacking]
-[Hangyeol] I was brushing my teeth. -[phone vibrates]
That was Minjae just now.
Huh? Why?
[Hangyeol] "Why aren't you picking up?
Do you all want to go to Dieland together?
How is the finite element analysis coming along?"
That's his text.
We haven't even touched it.
What should we say?
Should I say we're not done yet, but we're almost there?
No, wait.
Let me... [sighs]
Let me text him.
EOM TAEHO
[Taeho] Watch your language.
[announcer on PA] A train is approaching.
Please take a step back from the platform edge.
Jeez.
GORI'S SHOES
She's going to fall.
-[grunts] -[thuds]
[Minjae] Excuse me.
Drink this...
and use this to wipe it off.
I'm okay.
No, at least get the dirt and sand off for now.
If not cleaned right away, it could lead to ulcers and infection.
Wipe it off.
It broke, right? Give it to me.
Oh?
-[grunts] -What... That one wasn't broken.
You see, bipedal walking...
Walking on two legs means lifting two equal-length legs off the ground
one at a time, stepping with each, and moving your body forward.
But first, those two legs need to be the same length
for you to stay balanced. See?
Like this, and like this. That's how you walk. Got it?
Now try these on.
Try walking around in them.
There will always be another bus.
Don't run. You could fall.
Well, it's...
[passenger] Hi.
[announcer] This stop is the Engineering Building.
The next stop is the library main gate.
I'm Kim Haeun.
[softly] Kim Haeun.
I'm Lee Seongha.
Your name?
Lim Youjin.
Ten pieces?
[Youjin] Yes.
It's supposed to be at least five patterns,
so I just kept going...
No wonder you're top of your class.
Go see Professor Kang Miran after class. She asked you to stop by.
[Youjin] Okay.
Do you know what's going on?
[Subin] What?
Why does the professor want to see her?
Ah. It's probably about grad school. She wants her to join her lab.
-Is that so? -Yes.
How come I didn't know about it?
Uh...
You could've talked to me about this.
Nothing's been decided yet, so...
[Subin groans] Oh, no. That must hurt.
Yeah. Hey, thanks.
[Subin] Sure.
Put that on, and here's the pantyhose.
[Youjin in English] Thank you.
-[Subin in Korean] Should I do it for you? -Hmm-mmm.
[Youjin] There.
[Subin] How did you end up hurting it this badly?
-By the way, is he handsome? -Hmm?
Ah... Well, he's not super handsome or anything.
I'd say he's pretty average-looking, but not bad.
[Subin] Mmm...
How tall is he?
He's pretty tall.
Uh... He's pretty fit, but on the skinny side.
Ooh...
-He got off at the Engineering Building. -[Subin gasps] Really?
How come I've never seen him?
Was it love at first sight? Like fate?
No. I'm just feeling grateful. That's all.
Hmm.
Well, if you run into him again, that's got to be fate then.
We go to the same school.
If we meet again, it's coincidence, not fate.
And I'm graduating soon anyway.
Youjin, are you sure you don't want to go to grad school?
Come on, let's go together.
I want to study with you. Please?
Come on, join me.
[groans] Youjin, let's study together.
-Come in. -[door opens]
It's you, Youjin. Come on in.
Have a seat.
Did you have the talk? What did your parents say?
Ah, they said they were okay with me going to grad school.
See? I told you.
No parent would say no to their kid wanting to study.
But I thought maybe I should just get a job.
There's the tuition...
Tuition? You've been at the top of your class
and on scholarship this whole time.
What's there to worry about? Huh?
Grad schools also offer tuition aid for top students.
You don't have to worry.
I'm recommending this for a reason.
I really think you're a better fit for academia than the corporate world.
I'm not sure yet.
My grades are good, but I haven't won any design competitions.
No matter how hard I try, it doesn't work out.
Honestly, sometimes I wonder if maybe I just don't have a talent for this.
I don't know.
You just had bad luck with competitions.
And you can develop a talent for design or creativity later in life, too.
That's what happened to me.
When I see you like this, even your personality...
You really remind me of myself when I was younger.
I had the exact same worries back in undergrad.
Everyone around me was doing so well,
winning competitions left and right, doing great.
I kept asking myself, "Why can't I do it too, no matter how hard I try?"
But that's not how talent works.
Especially in academia,
the more work you put in, the more you get out of it.
And you know what?
Those people I used to envy? Those talented kids?
Do you know how many of them are still around now?
I'm the only one left.
The harder you work, Youjin, the more you'll get out of it.
Trust me.
I need a successor, too.
Someone who can take over after me.
Someone I can trust to pass everything on to.
I'll be able to guide you better.
-[Miran] Come in. -[door opens]
-Professor, it's Youngsoo. -[Miran] Hey.
Well, Reporter Lee is here.
-Okay. -[door opens]
I have an interview and a photo shoot with this magazine called Lady Sense.
-[Youjin] Ah. -If you don't mind,
could you help me with it?
Yes, I can help.
Good, thanks.
What's with your shoes, by the way?
[Youjin] Ah...
[Youngsoo] Hey, are you shopping or what? Hurry up.
-[Youjin] Okay. -[Youngsoo] And bring this too, okay?
[Youjin] Okay.
This time, the concept is "A Thousand Wishes."
So, just like folding a thousand paper cranes,
we're knitting a thousand hats to donate to children in war zones,
each one carrying a wish for peace.
When you fold paper cranes, each crane...
Aren't these the hats we made for our assignment?
Were they for donation?
Why didn't she tell us?
Is the donation under the school's name?
Come on. The professor's name is basically the school's name.
The triangle, you know.
That place in Africa where Cleopatra...
[reporter] You mean Egypt?
Not Egypt.
[reporter] What?
Ah! I meant a pyramid.
[reporter] Ah... Pyramid.
You know the symmetrical triangle, right?
Just have me sit right at the very top of it.
What?
Professor, could you move over just a little?
When this gets bound, the photo might get folded.
We agreed to run one shot across two full pages.
We already talked about this.
Right. We will have one shot across two pages, but--
[Miran] Exactly.
We don't need a bunch of little shots.
Let's do one big shot. Warm, but charismatic.
I want the concept to come through in one photo.
Yes, I'm all for doing one shot. I just wanted to say...
I think it'd be better if you could move just a little to the side.
Then the pyramid won't have as much charisma.
Ah, but...
Hmm...
Once this gets bound,
there could be a problem with the part that folds.
So, if you could move just a little to the side--
Then it won't be a pyramid anymore.
[yells] Warm charisma!
How many times do I have to repeat myself?
[reporter] All right, then...
Let's start the shoot.
[softly] Just do it.
[photographer] All right, very good. Look here. Okay.
-One, two. -[camera shutter clicks]
Now, give me a smile. Yes, very good. Okay, one, two.
All right. Warm charisma.
Yes, very good. Okay. One, two.
[whispering] By the way, we don't have a thousand, do we?
I don't think there are a thousand of them.
That's 200 at most.
[whispers] 200 sounds about right.
[Taeho] It's 73.5 years.
What do you think the average human life expectancy will be
by the time we reach that age?
-Well, something like... -[Taeho] Yeah?
...90, I think?
-[Taeho] What do you think, Chansoo? -100?
No, it's 120 years.
[Chansoo] Ah.
At the current rate of medical advancement,
human life expectancy will increase that much.
[Minjae] Oh, man.
Isn't that a good thing? It's good to live longer.
Well... [clears throat]
it's not just about living longer anymore.
From now on, it'll be about how you live your life.
[Chansoo] He's right. Living too long can be boring.
This year was so boring.
-It wasn't fun at all. -[Taeho] Right.
You guys are all talk.
Come on, stop talking and actually do something.
Hey, that's what we've been talking about.
Exactly. Stop the jibber-jabber and actually do something.
I mean, did you even get a single decent result from this beta test?
I think I'm finished.
I don't have any report to upload to the archive.
How do we not have a single paper with an impact factor of 7?
We're dead last in the entire school right now!
Minjae.
We were talking about life.
Yeah, exactly. Life...
Guys, this is about life.
I don't know how much longer I'll be able to keep working with you here in the lab.
I don't know how long my body and my health will allow me to keep going.
So...
we really have to finish Danny before I die. Okay?
You're gaslighting us again.
What did you just say?
[sighs] It's been 10 years since you were cured.
You're healthier than I am.
-Hey. -[Taeho] Now, I'm sicker than you.
-How many times do I say it? -[Taeho] I bet you'll live longer than me.
With cancer, there's no such thing as a complete cure.
[Taeho] No, you're completely cured.
What... No.
So, Minjae...
what I'm trying to say is,
we have lives outside of school, too. Okay?
Just like you write an experimental plan for the new year,
we could write one for our lives.
That's what I'm talking about.
[Hangyeol] I think it's a great idea.
How about we make a list of things we want to do, like a bucket list?
It could be traveling the world, or just simply traveling.
Or Michelin food. Going to a Michelin restaurant.
Or a girlfriend. Yeah, getting a girlfriend.
I'd like that. Dating. Getting married.
[chuckling] Yeah, exactly. Something like that.
Yeah? Minjae.
[Minjae] I don't need anything else.
Before I die, I just want our Danny to...
-[Taeho sighs] -[Hangyeol sighs]
-I'm just... -[Taeho sighing]
I mean... Guys, seriously?
PARK MINJAE'S BUCKET LIST 1. EAT CHICKEN
1. EAT CHICKEN - DONE
2. 100 PISTOL SQUATS - DONE
3. GET A DRIVER'S LICENSE 4. BUY A CAR
5. TRAVEL THE WORLD 6. START DATING
6. START DATING... ASK SOMEONE OUT?
FRIENDS
CHACHA
[Minjae] Chacha, what are you up to?
Hello?
Hey, I was about to leave work.
It's pretty busy because it's the end of the year. What's up?
It's just been a while since we last saw each other.
I thought we could grab a bite to eat.
But you seem busy.
Let's meet up when things slow down a bit.
Really?
Are you sure?
Let's meet up.
Yeah. In front of the school.
I know that place. When?
Okay. I'll see you then.
Okay. Bye.
FLOWERS
-[staff] Hello. -Hello.
-Hi. -I...
I want to buy some flowers.
[staff] Anything specific in mind?
Uh...
I've never bought flowers before, so...
[staff] Is it for your girlfriend?
-What? -[staff] Or for a birthday or a proposal?
Oh, no. Not girlfriend.
Just a friend.
In that case...
We've got hydrangeas, lilies, or carnations. They're gorgeous.
Can I just get the roses over there?
Sure. Which color would you like?
We've got red, yellow, and white.
Red, please.
Got it.
Hello.
[staff] Hello.
I'm from the Department of Fashion and Textiles.
[staff] One moment, please.
-Here you are. -Thank you.
[Subin] Youjin. The flower basket is ready.
Okay.
-Hey, one moment. -What?
What is it?
Hmm...
What's up? Someone you know?
Hmm.
Hi, Youngsoo. I'm at the flower shop now.
What?
Okay, oppa.
All right. Bye.
Kim Youngsoo?
Yes.
Why do you call him oppa?
I don't know. He told me to.
We're close, so I guess I can call him that.
You're not close at all.
Not with you.
That obnoxious bastard. If only he wasn't my senior...
He's a good person, though.
What? He's a good person?
[customer] Thank you. Bye.
-[staff] Have a good one. -[customer] Thanks.
-[Youngsoo] Hello. -Hello.
Do you want them in a bag?
No, I'll put them here.
Hey.
Yeah.
How long?
No, take your time.
Yeah, I know that place. Should I go there?
Uh...
Of course. That works too.
Then I'll head over there. I'll see you there.
Okay.
-[Seohyun] Hello, ma'am. -Hello.
-I'm here for an inspection today. -[owner] Okay.
[Seohyun] First, just check that the lens is clean.
Then make sure it's being charged every day.
Okay.
And this is checking if it's moving properly,
and if it's moving smoothly in a straight line.
And when you clean it, be careful about the wheels.
-[owner] Okay, got it. -Could you sign here?
-Thank you. -Sure.
All right.
Hey.
-[Seohyun] I'm sorry I'm late. -No, don't worry.
This is Nam Yoonsoo, my marketing team leader.
This is Park Minjae, my best friend from school.
Hello, I've heard a lot about you.
Hello, okay.
We're swamped with product launches for the spring moving season.
[Yoonsoo] Yeah.
Right. What do you think?
[Minjae] Hmm.
It's nice.
We're testing it out right now before the launch.
The display is 1080 by 1920.
How much does it weigh? It looks heavy.
Yeah, 65.
-[Minjae] Oh... -It's quite heavy because of the display.
It takes five hours to charge and can run for 12 to 15 hours.
So you and Ms. Cha went to the same high school?
-[Minjae] Yes. -And the same college too?
Right, yeah. It's a funny coincidence.
But I took the college entrance exam four times,
so I barely ever ran into her...
I started school years ahead of him.
He should be treating me like a senior,
but I get no respect because we went to high school together.
Come on, I treated you like a senior.
When?
Should I tell him how you got drunk and threw up all the time,
and I always had to clean it up?
She did that?
[Seohyun] Excuse me, could we get the menu, please?
[owner] Okay.
-No. -[both chuckle]
Now, let's hear a few words from Professor Kang Miran,
who's guided us all this time.
THANK YOU, PROFESSOR! TEACHER APPRECIATION DINNER
Hello, everyone. I'm Kang Miran.
Department of Fashion and Textiles has made it through another year.
Thanks to the faculty, my seniors and juniors,
we are sending off another outstanding group of graduates.
To all of you leaving the university behind
to make your way in the world,
now is the time to go out there
and pursue your ideals freely and to the fullest.
You can do it. Go out there and achieve your goals.
Of course, the world can be a harsh place.
There will be times when you stumble or experience failure.
But don't be afraid.
You have me and the university behind you.
Even after you leave, all of us who came before you
and those who will come after you remain closely and firmly connected.
So don't be afraid, take your perseverance and pride,
and confidently go out into the world.
But don't become arrogant.
The more accomplished you become,
the more important it is to remain humble and compassionate.
If you stay humble and keep working diligently,
you will definitely achieve your dreams.
-That turned into a bit of a lecture. -No, not at all.
But this is the last time you'll have to listen to one after you graduate,
so bear with me.
Ah, and I have some more good news to share.
Our very own Kim Youngsoo
will be joining Nagoya University as an assistant professor.
It's all thanks to you, Professor. Thank you.
Thank you.
-Remember that promise we made? -[Minjae] What?
If neither of us were married after 40, we'd save each other.
-Stop. -[Seohyun laughs]
You made a promise like that?
But, Minjae, I don't think you could get married even after 40.
Seriously, what are you going to do?
Are you single now?
Ah.
[exhales] Yes.
But why? You're attractive
and have a PhD from Seohan National.
I'm sure you're popular with women.
I don't have a PhD. I haven't gotten my degree yet.
Maybe you're too picky.
I've tried setting him up with coworkers and friends, but he always says no.
His standards are way up here. They're way too high.
Maybe he doesn't like blind dates.
Maybe he prefers meeting people organically.
Organic or not, he has to actually meet people first.
Minjae doesn't even try.
If you're done eating, let's go. I know you're busy.
[Yoonsoo] I got this.
No, I'll...
No, I can pay.
Why?
[Minjae] Come on, I want to pay.
A student doesn't have any money. Let him pay.
-I have money. -[Seohyun] What?
Are you two dating?
No, not really. But there's something going on.
I see.
He's kind, but he's kind of clueless.
A nice guy is the best.
He is really nice.
Hmm.
What do you think of him?
They say guys know other guys best, right?
If you think he's okay, I'll give him a chance.
So you'll go out with him if I say yes, and you won't if I say no?
Yes.
If you like him,
I like him.
If you want to go out with him, go for it.
Really?
Oh.
I'll go get the car. Wait here.
Come out when I call you.
[Seohyun] Thank you, bye.
-[owner] Bye. Come again. -[Seohyun] I will.
So you'll be an assistant professor there?
When? From this semester?
No.
I'm starting next semester.
But it all happened so suddenly,
I haven't had time to prepare for anything.
I'm so overwhelmed right now.
You must be so busy.
I'm happy for you, though. Congratulations.
So... Nagoya University is in Japan, right?
Where in Japan is it?
In Nagoya, obviously. It's called Nagoya University.
Are you dumb?
I mean, Jeju National University is in Jeju Island.
Pusan National University is in Busan.
Where's Daegu University? In Daegu, obviously.
Why do you say such dumb things?
[Youjin] Not all of Jeju is Jeju National University.
There are different regions in there, like Jeju City.
Why are you grilling me about the address?
Who are you? Are you a district mayor?
A community center employee?
Why pick a fight on a good day?
-I didn't pick a-- -[Subin] I need to use the restroom.
-I should get going too. -Hey.
[Youngsoo] Professor, are you heading out?
Youngsoo, Subin, thanks so much for preparing the event.
-[both chuckle] -[Subin] Please. We didn't do anything.
Right, Professor. This... It's nothing much.
Just a gift and some letters from the students.
[exclaims] Why did you even take those?
[Youngsoo] No, they're really just letters.
Ah, and these are some pastries.
They're from Maman Bakery, your favorite. You only eat their pastries.
They're for when you get hungry while working on your research later.
Gosh, being this kind should be illegal.
[Youngsoo chuckling] It's nothing. It's cold out. You should head home.
[Miran] Okay, sure. Thank you.
[Youngsoo] I'll stay in touch, Professor.
[Miran] Yeah, let's. Thank you.
-Thanks, Subin. Okay. -I'll put it here. No worries.
-Thank you. -All right, get back home safe!
Have a safe trip home. Bye.
Please get her home safely, sir.
These little suck-ups.
Hey, Subin.
[Subin] Yes?
How about we go grab one more drink?
Ah...
I don't know. You look pretty drunk already.
What do you mean, I'm drunk?
Okay, then just beer... let's go have just one more beer.
I'll ask Youjin too, then.
No.
Let's just go without Youjin. Just the two of us.
Oh...
-Excuse me. -Yes?
Where's the restroom?
It's over there, in the back.
Thank you.
I almost made a total fool of myself.
I'd never live it down. [groans]
Hi.
What's your name?
[robot] Hello, my name is Arti.
How can I help you?
-[staff] Excuse me. -Yes?
[staff] Just leave it. We can do it later.
No. I'm almost done.
[Youjin] Hey, what's going on?
Hey, wait!
Jeez! What the hell?
-Somebody call the police! Now! -[Youngsoo grunting]
-What? Police. -[Youjin] Hurry!
[Youngsoo] That hurts!
-Call the police... No, let me. -[Youngsoo groans]
-[Youjin] Hurry! -[Youngsoo] That hurts. [groans]
Whoa. It's right around the corner, but we're not moving an inch.
Was there perhaps an accident? The alleys around here are very narrow.
I should call and tell him to cross the road.
-Oh. -[Youjin] It's okay.
Hello?
Ah.
I'm okay. I left early.
Yeah. I didn't get to say goodbye.
Mmm.
Ah.
You're driving now, so let's talk later. Okay, bye.
Hey, thank you for helping us.
Don't worry about it.
But are you really okay?
Did you hurt yourself anywhere?
No, I'm okay. I'm fine.
GWANAK CENTRAL POLICE STATION
So the three of you go to the same school?
Yes, but we're in different departments.
I don't study Fashion. I study something else.
[officer] What do you study?
-Mechanical engineering. -[officer] Ah.
-A graduate student. Okay. -[officer] Okay.
Do we have to hire a lawyer or something?
That's what they do in TV shows.
We're interviewing you as a witness, not a suspect, so you won't need a lawyer.
Detective. Please make sure
that bastard gets the maximum sentence and never gets out.
-[officer] Okay. -[shudders]
Then just tell me exactly what you saw. You can take your time.
So, when I went in...
[exhales] ...that bastard had Subin pinned against the wall
and was trying to force a kiss on her.
She was saying no, but he just kept forcing himself on her.
He shoved her against the wall with his body,
pinned her arms so she couldn't move,
and then he forced a kiss on her.
I mean, it wasn't a kiss. It was sexual assault. Anyway...
You saw it too, right?
What?
He's a witness. He was there with me.
I'm telling the truth, right? You saw it too, right?
No, I didn't see it.
You didn't see it?
I mean, by the time I got there, it was already over.
Her friend got him under control pretty quickly.
She was on top of the guy, who was lying on the ground.
But...
I did hear a scream.
I think it was a woman screaming.
Ah... All right. Got it.
By the way, you were right there with us. How could you not have seen it?
Well, as I said, it was already over when I got there.
You got the situation under control pretty quickly.
But still...
You could've said
you thought I was telling the truth.
Why did you say you didn't see anything?
[Minjae] Because I didn't see it.
I said I didn't see it because I didn't.
I have to tell the truth.
[Youjin] No, I'm not saying you should've said you saw it.
No, that's not what I meant.
Besides, if I say the wrong thing, I could be making a false accusation.
Then there could be another victim.
[Youjin] What do you mean, another victim?
Are you siding with that asshole?
I'm not siding with him.
When you give a statement, you have to get the facts straight.
By the way, I saw you taking pictures.
What?
[Youjin] I saw it.
You were taking pictures in front of us earlier.
-What about it? -Can I see them?
There might be something in there we can use as evidence.
There's nothing.
I was just taking pictures of the robot servers going around.
I know. But you might've caught something else in the shot.
So please, let us see.
I'm not comfortable doing that.
Why? What makes you uncomfortable?
I mean, it's rude to ask to look through someone's phone.
No, I just want to see if you happened to capture anything
that could be evidence.
I'm asking a favor.
I said there's nothing. You're making me uncomfortable.
Right, why does that make you uncomfortable?
I just want to see the pictures. You don't have weird photos, do you?
What do you mean weird photos? I don't have those.
[Youjin] Yeah, exactly. So just show me.
If you want to see it so badly, go get a search warrant.
Then I'll show you.
A search warrant...
Come on, you're really being difficult.
What? I'm the one being difficult here?
I stepped in to help, and now you're asking even more of me.
What more am I asking? I just want to see your phone.
And when exactly did you help me? I handled it all by myself.
[weakly] Hey, Youjin.
Hey. Are you okay? I'm sorry.
Wait here. I'll call you a cab now.
I can call a cab myself. I don't need your help.
-No, you take care of her. I'll call one. -[Youjin] What?
I said I don't need your help. Go.
Just get lost already.
-[soft whirring] -[latch clicks]
-[chimes] -[door unlocks]
Damn it.
What the...
Hello? Mom.
Hey.
Oh, no. Did you give her medicine?
Yeah, no wonder Subin got sick.
Okay. All right. Bye.
[Yongseok] What did she say?
Ah, Subin's sick, so Youjin will stay with her tonight.
She's not sick. She's just sick from drinking too much.
[exclaims] Do you know what an appreciation dinner is?
Isn't it just everyone getting wasted together?
Seohan National University is where the country's brightest minds go.
It's where they come together to thank their professors.
Why would she get wasted there?
Mom, anyone can get sick if they drink too much.
I know. I mean, Seohan National University students,
the brightest minds in the country, wouldn't drink that much.
Honey, I saw on TV that kids get their intelligence from their mothers.
So it turns out Youjin gets all her brains from me.
What about me? What does that make me?
I take after you too. What about my grades?
I didn't give birth to you.
Then who did?
My first love in high school.
She gave birth to you.
What? Is that true?
So your first love is my biological mother or something?
It means your mom is my first love.
Jeez.
Why would you say it like that? This is so annoying.
-[Miyoung] Hey, go to bed. -Come on, just a minute.
Go on and get to bed.
I'm so tired.
FAVORITES 23 IMAGES
SELECT ITEMS
23 ITEMS SELECTED MOVE 23 PHOTOS TO TRASH?
NO FAVORITE PHOTOS
SEOHAN NATIONAL UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
Goodness.
[Youngsoo] Professor.
How did you...
Professor. Professor!
Professor, wait. Professor!
Get home safe.
The person you are calling is unavailable.
SUBIN, I'M AT YOUR DOOR
INCOMING CALL PROFESSOR KANG MIRAN
QUIET YET POWERFUL WARM CHARISMA
PROFESSOR KANG MIRAN "A THOUSAND WISHES" PROJECT
I hear he's in the hospital now. You should go and apologize to him.
Apologize?
Why should I do that?
Violence is never acceptable, no matter the circumstances.
And to your senior at that? Don't you have any respect?
If he's my senior, I think he should act like it first.
I know. He got drunk and made a mistake.
I'm not saying what he did was okay. But you're from the same school.
Can't you just let this one little mistake slide?
It's not just a mistake. It's a crime.
So, now it's a crime?
Things can happen when a man and a woman are dating.
Dating?
They're not. Did Kim Youngsoo say they were dating?
That's all a lie.
No, that's what Subin said.
She said you and Youngsoo never really got along.
She said she couldn't be honest about it because of you.
That can't be true...
That can't be true.
Subin is a kind, soft-hearted girl.
She must've been putting up with a lot because of you.
Anyway, let's just have you apologize and leave it at that, okay?
Blowing this up just embarrasses the school
and reflects badly on us all.
Let's leave it at that and move on.
No. I can't do that.
Whether they were dating or not, what he did was wrong.
He never should've done it.
He deserved to get hit, and I have no intention of apologizing.
So you're not going to listen to me, either?
He didn't act like my senior.
And right now,
I don't think you're acting like a professor.
What?
Isn't it a teacher's job to correct and guide students when they do wrong?
Shouldn't that come before the school's reputation or your pride?
Are you lecturing me right now?
You're obviously so smart.
Who am I to try to guide or teach someone like you, huh?
You won't listen to a word I say, so I can hardly call you my student.
If you have nothing further to say,
may I be excused?
Go.
The moment you walk out that door, you are no longer my student.
So from now on, don't you ever mention my name or this school to anyone.
Are you threatening me now?
As if someone as proud as you would feel threatened by this.
Yes.
I know how small this field is.
And honestly, it does scare me.
Thanks to you, I've learned a valuable lesson.
Thank you for everything.
Take care of yourself.
[passerby] Excuse me.
I don't think you're allowed to eat in here.
Right. I'm not a student here.
I'm a graduate.
No one can hold my grades over my head
or threaten to keep me from graduating, so I'm just going to do whatever I want.
I'm free now, just drifting through life like duckweed on the water.
Mmm-hmm.
What do you think?
[passerby] Mmm...
Yeah, it's beautiful.
[Youjin] It's beautiful and creative, isn't it?
I think I have a pretty good eye,
but I find clothing a difficult medium to work with.
Even when I know what I want to convey, I can't quite turn it into a design,
and I end up copying others' work.
But anyway, that's all just an excuse.
At the end of the day,
I didn't have what it takes to be an artist or a creative director.
So there's no point blaming anyone else.
It wasn't anyone else's fault. I just didn't have enough talent.
Hello?
Who is this?
[in English] Yeah.
Ah, I couldn't find the Natural Sciences building.
So, I'm at the art museum right now.
-[in Korean] Please wait here for a sec. -Okay.
I checked with the legal team,
and they said it'd be fine if I have your signature.
But how did you know my phone number?
If you know someone's name and school, you can easily find their number.
I still haven't fully forgiven you, though.
But I didn't do anything wrong.
Please follow me.
[Seohyun] I pulled the audio from the robot,
but it was pretty far away.
Listen to this.
How is it?
Could you turn up the volume?
[Seohyun] Hold on.
That's as loud as it goes.
-It is? -[Seohyun] Yeah.
-[Minjae] Take a listen. -Hmm.
Can you hear it?
Do you hear anything?
Uh...
Here.
I made you come all this way for nothing.
I'm sorry.
Not at all.
You went out of your way to help with all this.
-I'm the one who should be sorry. -Uh...
And even if there had been evidence, it wouldn't have helped much.
What?
Apparently, Subin was dating that bastard.
She didn't tell me because she was worried about how I'd react.
Ah...
I see.
But even if they're dating, what he did was still wrong.
Right?
Yeah, it's wrong.
And why didn't she tell me she was dating him?
Isn't it strange that she kept it from me?
Hmm...
No, that's not strange. She can do that.
What?
Even though you two were very close, she might not have wanted to tell you.
Everyone has secrets.
I don't have any.
I'm sure you do.
I don't.
Haven't you ever had a crush on someone? Or...
Any habits or weaknesses you don't want anyone to know about,
or something that hurt you?
Everyone has at least one thing they can't tell their friends
or even their family.
Do you have something like that?
No, I don't.
Well, you're graduating soon anyway.
Try to put the bad experience behind you and make a fresh start.
A fresh start...
Your friend has her own life to live, and so do you.
You're studying mechanical engineering, right?
Yes, I'm doing my PhD in robotics.
I haven't actually earned the degree yet. I'm still just a student.
What first drew you to mechanical engineering?
There's usually a story behind it.
There is.
Have you ever read Slam Dunk?
-Slam Dunk? -[Minjae] Yes.
The comic series?
No, I haven't read it.
You haven't? You really should. It's a masterpiece.
Uh...
How I got into mechanical engineering is kind of like Slam Dunk.
[announcer] The 687 bus will arrive shortly.
The bus is here.
Aren't you going to get on?
Ah, this one doesn't go to my place.
-[card reader beeps] -[door hisses]
We've met at a bus stop before.
Do you remember?
Ah...
So, about Slam Dunk. How is it similar?
Ah.
Before Hanamichi Sakuragi first joins the basketball team,
Haruko Akagi asks him, "Do you like basketball?"
And he goes, "Yes, I like it. Very, very much..."
What?
[yelling] "Yes, I like it. Very, very much."
BETWEEN STEPS
But why do you suddenly want to switch to a completely different major?
He was sitting side by side with a woman, looking at something on a laptop.
[Youjin] Boyfriend? Why do you care if I have a boyfriend or not?
[Minjae] What do you mean, be honest?
[Hangyeol] Are you dating that woman?
[Youjin] Park Minjae isn't exactly my type, either.
I can't stand guys like him.
[Minjae] What were you doing while she caused trouble?
[Youjin] He's smart, handsome, and tall.
What if he doesn't like me?